Hello friends, my name is Himanshu Israni and I am from PaisaWatch. My father has been in the insurance field for 36 years. Today we will talk about ICICI Lad Elevate, which is a comprehensive plan for various medical needs. So let us now talk about some of the great benefits of this plan: Inpatient hospitalization, day care treatment, modern treatment, AYUSH treatment, domicile hospitalization, donor expenses, domestic road ambulance and bariatric surgery. All these things are covered up to the sum insured. Guaranteed cumulative bonus: In this, you will get 20% off sum insured for every claim-free year. Maximum up to 100% and it will not reduce on future claims. Reset benefit: In this, 100% of sum insured will be reset for any illness. For the same person, your waiting period for the same illness will be 45 days and for other illnesses of the same person, there will be no waiting period. In the wellness program, you can get a discount of up to 30% on Wellness Point.
Pre and post hospitalization cover is 90 and 180 days. Inpatient treatment for USI donors and surrogate mothers will get up to Rs 5 lakh. Let us now talk about some of the important add-ons and optional covers. First comes the Jump Start add-on cover, which covers asthma, diabetes, hypertension, hyperlipidemia, and obesity from 31 days. If you opt for this benefit, you will have to opt for it for three years. This cover is only available at the inception of the policy or at the time of renewal. Second is the Be Fit cover, which covers all non-hospitalization expenses up to 65 years. You will get a cashless claim in this. Now, what I am going to tell you about is the industry's first add-on cover called Infinite Care. In Infinite Care, you will get unlimited sum insured for any one claim. You can opt for this at the inception of the policy and the first renewal of the policy once you have
If you claim it, you cannot opt ​​for it again. The next point is Power Booster Guaranteed Super Plus, which is an industry first add-on cover, in which you get 100% of the sum insured, but with an annual maximum up to unlimited sum insured, which will be relative to the claim. If you opt out of this, whatever cumulative bonus you have earned becomes zero. Now let us talk about Claim Protector, in which non-medical items and consumables which are not covered in health insurance will be covered. The next point is Inflation Protector, which we can understand with an example. If we assume that inflation is at 6% and we have taken a sum insured of ₹ 1 lakh, then when we have applied the inflation protector for ₹ 1 lakh at the inception of the policy, then your inflation protector is not applicable. At the time of renewal, the inflation protector gets activated, due to which your sum insured is less than ₹ 1 lakh.  10600.
Now let us talk about Domestic Air
Ambulance, in which you will get services
by a healthcare provider or an authorized
air ambulance. All the expenses
covered in this are covered up to the annual sum insured.
Let us now talk about the Combination
Benefit, in which if your
hospitalization exceeds 10 days,
you get a fixed allowance of up to Rs. 1000 once
per policy year. Let us now talk about the
next optional benefit which is
Nursing at Home. In Nursing at Home, you
get up to Rs. 1000 per day, maximum of 10
days for a qualified nurse
who comes to your home for medical services after
hospitalization. The next optional cover is
Compassionate Visit, in which if the hospitalization
exceeds 10 days, the immediate
member gets up to Rs. 1000 for any air
ticket and railway ticket. There are some other optional benefits in this plan
like Health Checkup.
In Health Checkup, you will get 0.5 of sum insured,
maximum up to  Up to ₹ 000 and the
listed test will be on cashless basis In case of
critical illness also you will get up to sum
insured up to maximum of ₹ 50 lakh
and it will be covered till the age of 50 years For
adults
Personal accident In personal accident
you will get up to sum insured up to maximum of ₹
50 lakh and it will be covered till the age of 65 years
For adults only Dependent
accommodation benefit You will get up to ₹ 000 per day
Maximum up to 10 days Durable
medical equipment cover You will get up to sum
insured up to maximum of ₹ 5 lakh with
base sum insured Tele consultation will be given to you
according to the sum insured
which you choose
You also get discounts in this plan like
civil discount You get civil discount
on 1 to 15 years depending on your civil
score and you get discount that if
you are taking a 2 year policy then you will get ₹ 10 per day
and ₹ 3  If you are taking a policy for 1 year then you will
get a discount of 15% We are
saving the best for last Room Modify Room
Modify Twin sharing room Get 1%
off sum insured for normal room and 2%
off sum insured for ICU Get
sum insured options up to 7.5 lakhs Let
us now talk about the policy terms Sum
insured ranges from ₹ 1 lakh to unlimited sum insured Entry age is 15 years to
125 years The age of dependent child is up
to 30 years Cover type is Individual and
Family Floater Tenor is 20 and 3 years
Zone which has four zones and there is no
zone based copay Roll over sum insured is
20 lakhs The guideline
pricing is age band wise
Age band is 5 years Maximum of two adults
and three children Let us now talk about
exclusions Before the policy,
disease or  Injuries are not covered for two years. There is a
30-day waiting period for medical expenses. Self-
inflicted injuries are also not covered.
Substance use is also not covered. Vision and
dental care are also not covered. Childbirth, including
complicated delivery and
C-section, is not covered.
Pregnancy is covered.